Matthew Lluís Web Developer

linkedin.com/in/mwlluis github.com/MattTheMicrowave

About Me...

I am an Austin-based Web Developer specializing in Front-End Engineering, but presently learning more of the Back-End. I am most experienced with the HTML, CSS, and JavaScript languages along with the Bootstrap and AngularJS frameworks. I like to build, I like to share, and I really (really) like to learn.

Experience

February 2016 - present

khmertuktuk.com, khmertuktuk.com/spanish.html

Webmaster/Web Developer

This is a website that I created and maintain for my friend's tuk-tuk service in Siem Reap Cambodia. It was built from scratch in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I also built a Spanishlanguage version.

August 2015 – present

eyehategod.ee, facebook.com/OfficialEyehateGod

Web Developer/Contributor/Administrator

These are the official websites of the New Orleans-based band, I maintain, design, and edit the client-side components of eyehategod.ee, coding in HTML, CSS, and Javascript languages.

May 2013 – present

thekingsofmetal.com/blog

Writer/Administrator

This is a travel blog site, built with WordPress, that I write for and maintain using the WordPress platform to edit and modify the layout and functionality of the content.

Skills

Portfolio: matthewlluis.com/portfolio.html

 $Languages:\ HTML,\ CSS,\ JavaScript,\ JQuery,$

PHP, Python

Frameworks: Bootstrap, AngularJS

Software: Brackets, Git, WordPress, Adobe Creative Suite, Microsoft Office Suite

Additional Languages: Fluency in Spanish

(Conversing, Reading, Writing)

Education

Austin Coding Academy, Austin, TX Completed Front-End Intermediate Track, 2015

Speakeasy Language School, Barcelona, Spain Completed Intensive Spanish Program, 2014

The University of Texas at Austin, Austin, TX PhD in Biochemistry, 2009

University of South Florida, Tampa, FL B.S. in Chemistry, 2004

Contact



(512) 806-9176



matthew.w.lluis@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mwlluis



github.com/MattTheMicrowave



mateo.lluis